♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
You really thought Atoy
was Karla's brother.
[Siony] Then why did you get mad?
Don't you want Atoy to be your brother?
I wish he were, but…
you shouldn't just wish for things.
There are consequences.
I know you were hurt.
PREVIOUSLY
[Audrey, in English] And I'm sorry.
[in English] I'm sorry.
[Dmitri, in English]
You seem like a good father.
[in English] But I don't want you
around my daughter.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you didn't need to know.
Dad, be honest with me.
You don't want Atoy for me, do you?
[in English] I'm just worried about you
and my granddaughter.
[Audrey] Atoy is a good man.
[Dmitri, in English]
Everyone has a secret, child.
Especially someone like Atoy.
[in English] You can't get over
that businessman,
because of what he did to your face, huh?
[clamoring]
- [thumps]
- [Kurt panicking]
[in English] Alexei! What are you doing
to my brother, huh?!
[in English]
Your brother is the one who hurt me first!
I want you to check his profile.
His name is Alexei Sokolov.
[Atoy] I need Ben gone for three hours,
so I can do what I need to do.
Is this where you get the replacement ID?
What's your name?
[Atoy] Ben Laput.
Uh, Laput,
letter U, not letter O.
[device beeping]
What are you carrying here?
‪[dramatic stinging]
[music swells, concludes]
[beeping]
[suspicious music playing]
What's this?
[music swells]
Ground meat.
Do you want some?
No. Maybe that's not enough for you.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
I also have three eggs here.
Do you want them?
No, just go inside.
Okay.
Thank you.
[suave theme music playing]
We even drank together at the baptism of…
of-- What's this?
Why aren't we drinking now?
Because, you know,
there's a newly opened beer house here!
It's open at this hour.
Come with me.
Bro, bro, I don't know you.
- Huh?
- I don't-- don't remember you.
- No!
- Go home, go home!
No. Come on, bro. Just come with me.
I'll take care of you tomorrow.
I'll treat you, bro.
Come on, join me. Come on, join me here.
- Sorry. I really don't know you.
- Huh?
Bro, come on!
- You know me!
- What's wrong with you!
Come on, bro. Come on!
[groans]
Wait.
My… My wallet.
My wallet-- My wallet. Give me my wallet.
Did you take my wallet? Where's my wallet?
I didn't take anything from you!
- Huh?!
- I'm helping you, right?!
And you're accusing me?!
You're really drunk!
Atoy, make sure you double
my pay for this.
I'm risking my face here.
[clears throat]
Ah-- Ah, wa-wait. My… My… My wallet.
Give me my wallet, or I'll beat you up!
I'll beat you up if you don't
give me my wallet!
[groans]
Ouch, ouch.
[panting] Atoy.
[tense music playing]
[Emerson] Ben. Sir Ben.
What's happening? B-Ben. Sir Ben.
Wait. Hey, wake up, wake up!
Sir Ben!
Oh, no! He might be dead.
Hmm, Atoy said
only three hours, not forever.
Sir Ben! Wake up, wake up!
[anxious music playing]
Hello, sir?
I'm already here on the rooftop.
But we have a little problem.
I heard the security.
Looks like they're on high alert
and want to call Alexei Sokolov.
[Mercado on the phone] That's a problem.
If they see Alexei Sokolov's profile,
they'll know your identity
yesterday was fake.
If that happens,
the embassy will be alerted.
They'll either lock down the embassy
or move your target.
And it'll be harder for us
if that happens.
Exactly! So, you need to hurry, Atoy.
[in English] Copy, sir. Ready to execute.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
What now?
Help! Help!
[panting]
Oh no, maybe he needs mouth-to-mouth.
‪[quirky sting]
[sneaky music playing]
[mutters]
[whimpering]
[gasping]
Sir Ben. Oh, he's breathing!
Sir Ben, what happened to you?
Sir Ben, wake up. Wake up, wake up.
Come on. I'll help you.
What happened to you?
[grunts]
You're heavy.
Come here.
[grunts]
Come here. I'll help you.
[groans] Come on.
Here, ride here.
What happened to you?
Really, what--
Sir Ben, did you get a heart attack?
[grunting]
[Emerson] Okay, hurry.
[grunts] You have to double
my pay, Atoy, okay.
Hmph! Oh, stuck. [grunts]
[suave theme music playing]
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[both, in Russian] Good day!
[in English] My friend, how are you?
[in English] Mr. Ambassador.
[in English] I would like you to meet
my lovely daughter, Audrey.
- Audrey, Viktor Petrov.
- Hello.
- [in English] The ambassador of Zahran.
- [in English] Pleasure to meet you, sir.
[in English] You never told me
you had such a beautiful daughter.
[in English] The pleasure is mine.
[in English] And, uh, where is husband?
[in English] Oh, she is single.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] That is impossible.
‪[Dmitri chuckles]
[in English] In that case, we have to find
somebody for you tonight.
[in English] Um, I may not
be married, but…
I'm already taken, sir.
[in English] Well,
she may change her mind,
depending on who
will be introduced to her.
[in English] Okay.
Let us just enjoy the party.
[in English] Do you like classical music?
[in English] Yes.
[in English] Number one violinist
of Zahran, he is playing tonight.
[in English] That sounds wonderful, sir.
[in English] So, let us go meet my friend.
- [in English] Come, come with me.
- [Dmitri, in English] Thank you.
[indistinct]
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
- [Karla] Your food.
- Thank you.
Oh, Karla! Wait.
Help me here so we can finish faster.
I don't want to, Mom.
Atoy isn't here.
He'll be home later tonight.
[pensive music playing]
How long will you keep avoiding Atoy?
He might notice that you're avoiding him.
Then let him notice.
He'll ask questions.
[unsettling music playing]
I can't do what you're doing, Mom.
I can't face Brother Atoy
because I feel guilty.
But you didn't do anything wrong.
That's the point.
I didn't do anything wrong,
but I'm ashamed
of how you deceived his family.
I'm not like you, who's thick-faced.
[tense music playing]
[dramatic sting]
Karla.
Karla--
[sobs]
[in English] Oh, you are going
to serve that?
[in English] Yes, sir.
[in English] No, no, no.
That is not what the ambassador likes.
[in English] Yes, sir.
But there's no other wine here.
[in English] There is in the office.
I will get it.
Okay.
[pensive music playing]
[suspicious music playing]
[tense music playing]
‪[music intensifies]
[in English] You will like
my friends, Dmitri.
[in English] It will be an honor.
[in English] Dad, I think
I'll stay behind.
I just have to call someone.
[in English] All right.
[in English] No. You cannot be alone.
[in English] Uh, wait.
- Daphne.
- [Daphne, in English] Yes, sir?
[in English] Where is Samir?
- [in English] Look for him.
- [in English] Okay, sir.
[elegant classical music playing]
[in English] You will like
the head of my security.
[in English] He is tough, but very nice.
[in English] He's ex-military
and single too.
[in English] Maybe later.
[in English] Interesting.
[in English] Let's go?
[in English] Um, get her a drink.
[rousing music playing]
[tense music playing]
[line rings]
[phone ringing]
Audrey?
[in English] Uh, hello, Atoy.
I-I just wanted to let you know
that I'm here now
at the embassy of Zahran.
What?! What are you doing at the embassy?
Um, Dad brought me to the party,
because the ambassador is his friend.
If you can, maybe don't join.
Don't go there.
Why?
Is there a problem?
I'm here too.
I-- I'm finishing a mission.
What? Why? What are you--
Why did you come?
What?!
Whe-- Where are you?
Whatever!
Where are you?!
- [in English] Sir Samir?
- [in English] Yes?
[in English] The ambassador
is looking for you.
- [in English] Uh, help me.
- [Daphne, in English] Yes, sir.
[in English] Take two of this.
[tense music playing]
[in English] Look at this guy.
[in English] What a loser.
[Audrey] Oh, are you here at the event?
[in English] Hello?
Hello? Why aren't you answering?
Okay, fine. We'll talk later.
Take care.
[in Russian] You're dumb!
[in English] Get off your phone
and get back to work!
[tense music playing]
KARLA, WHERE ARE YOU?
I'VE GOT A GIG FOR YOU
SO, CAN YOU DRIVE FOR ME?
[melancholic music playing]
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU AREN'T REPLYING TO ME
ARE YOU OKAY?
ALWAYS REMEMBER, IF YOU HAVE
A PROBLEM, YOU CAN ALWAYS COME TO ME
[phone blips]
Karla!
- [in English] Babe, where are you going?
- To Karla.
But we'll be late.
This will just take a moment, okay?
I'll just check on her.
Where did she go?
Oh, she already left.
Come on, babe. Let's go.
- [line rings, then blips]
- [knock on door]
Miss Cita.
Hey, Paldo, come in.
- Good day.
- Come in.
Did you see Karla outside?
Uh, I ran into her earlier.
She was scowling.
I'm sure you fought again.
Um, not really.
Ah. My-- My friend, uh, Jeffrey,
wants to have clothes tailored.
Is Atoy here?
Oh, Atoy isn't here right now.
Is that so? I also stopped by Emerson's.
He wasn't there either.
Do the tailors have a convention today?
They're both out.
[chuckles softly]
Probably not.
Just send him here
so I can take his measurements, okay?
What's his name again?
- Jeffrey. Jeffrey.
- Jeffrey.
Paldo, thanks for the referral.
- Of course, Miss Cita.
- All right.
[Emerson] Wait. Sir Ben.
[pensive music playing]
Please take care of--
What happened to the patient?
I don't, uh-- I just…
I just saw him faint.
On the street, I just saw him faint.
Ah. He's not your relative?
Oh? No, no, no.
I'm just a… I'm just a good Samaritan.
Um, you need to sign this first.
Me?
[heavy breathing]
I don't know. I don't know the--
Um, excuse me. Just a moment.
[heavy breathing, sharp exhale]
No, eh.
[line rings]
- Hello?
- [Emerson on the phone] Atoy.
Uh, you need to help me here with Ben.
Looks like this guy won't be able
to return to the building.
Uh, I think I killed him.
[machine clangs]
[ominous music playing]
We-- We're here now at the hospital.
The problem is, bro, I might go to jail.
I don't want to go to jail, bro. Help me.
Hello?
[suspicious music playing]
Atoy, are you still alive?
Or are you just busy? Atoy!
[line beeping]
Atoy!
[tense music playing]
Hmm, back, length.
- [Cita, in English] Twenty-seven.
- Yes.
[Cita, in English] Neck.
Miss Cita.
[Cita] Uh-huh? Seventeen. Oh?
Is this still working?
It just needs a little fixing.
[in English] Bicep, mmm.
Why don't you sell this?
There's a junk shop here
that will take it.
Oh, no, Atoy won't allow it.
That's Delfin's old machine.
[somber music playing]
Do you want it loose
or really fitted to the body?
Like this.
Ah, okay.
Like this, fitted.
[Cita] Hmm…
[Cita mutters]
That's why this is so old school.
Sir Delfin's death anniversary
must be near.
Oh, yes! You still remember that?
[music swells]
[car engine revving]
- [tires screeching]
- [crashes]
[car engine revving]
[people panicking]
[sinister music playing]
Stupid meddler.
Boss, that's Atoy's father, boss.
You might have killed him.
Boss, he didn't do anything wrong to us.
Sir Delfin was kind.
Everyone who knew him here in Tabang Lupa…
They all know that.
[melancholic music playing]
You know…
Sir Delfin really had an impact here.
[sighs] Just write your name
and contact number.
Do you know what Delfin said
when you were still a child?
[sighs]
He said you were a good kid,
and he was sure
you'd grow up to be a good man.
Really?
Mm, but then you fell in
with bad company, though.
You've changed now, haven't you?
And if Delfin
were alive today, I'm sure…
he'd be proud of you.
[melodramatic music playing]
Really?
Of course!
[phone ringing]
Hello?
I'll go there.
Okay.
Jeff, tell Benj I won't be able to join.
[pensive music playing]
Miss Cita, I just need to run an errand.
[Cita] Okay. Take care.
All right.
Your contact number
is already here, right?
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] To grace us
with beautiful music,
please listen to the number one
violinist in our country, Zahran.
[in English] This is Sasha!
[audience applauding]
[classical violing music playing]
[in English] Sasha is amazing.
[in English] Number one in our country.
[Viktor, in English]
What about you, Audrey?
[in English] Do you like
this type of music?
[in English] Yes, sir.
I like it very much. [smirks]
[in English] Oh,
and you would like this too.
[in English] Samir,
this is my dear friend, Dmitri.
[Samir, in English]
Nice to meet you, Sir Dmitri.
[in English] And this beautiful girl
is Audrey.
[in English] This is Samir.
He is the one I've been telling you about.
[Samir, in English] Hello, Ms. Audrey.
[in English] Uh, Dmitri,
come with me to my office,
because there is something
I want to show you.
[in English] Sure.
[tense music playing]
[in English] Dad.
[in English] Would you excuse us
for a moment?
Dad, please stay here.
[in English] Please, just stay here.
[music swells]
[in English] Is everything all right?
[in English] Uh, I was just telling Dad
that I think it would be rude if we left
while Sasha is still playing.
[classical violin music playing]
[in English] What's really the problem?
Dad, I came with you here.
And now you'll just leave me
with that man?
- [in English] You're exaggerating.
- [sighs]
He looks kind.
[in English] Get to know him.
[pensive music playing]
[clears throat]
[in English] Hello, Ms. Audrey.
Shall we have a drink?
[in English] Oh, that's a good idea.
[in English] I'm getting thirsty
too, child.
[in English] Yes.
- [in English] Look. Samir, right?
- [indistinct]
[in English] Um, I'm sure
you're a great guy.
[in English] But I already have a daughter
and a boyfriend.
[in English] That is no problem.
[in English] But is he better than me?
[scoffs]
[in English] Of course,
and better-looking too.
[suspicious music playing]
[lock clicks]
[tense music playing]
[in English] I thought
you liked the music, Audrey.
[in English] Why-- Why did you join us?
[sinister music playing]
[in English] I just want to make sure
that my dad doesn't do something silly!
[chuckles, in English] Come on, Audrey.
[in English] What do you think
I will do there?
[in English] Don't you trust your father?
[chuckles]
[in English] You have
a very protective daughter, Dmitri.
[Victor chuckles]
[Victor, in English] Come.
[intense music playing]
[device blipping]
[door lock clicks]
- [electronic blipping]
- [tense music playing]
You cannot leave the group!
Who's leaving? You don't want to anymore?
- [Red] That's fine.
- Thank you, boss.
Boss, you let him go?
[Red] I just gave him a head start.
‪UP NEXT
[in English] The Sokolov brothers
who attended the summit are impostors.
[in English] Are you sure?
[in English] I am sure, sir.
[in English] We have been compromised.
[dramatic stinging]
- [music swells]
- [machine clangs]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias